Nasa nasa.
美国宇航局
Nana.
娜娜
Girl, this time you're all alone,
女孩 这次你是孤身一人
but it's time you started living.
但也是你开始生活的时候了
It's time you let someone else do some giving love is all around know me,
该是你让别人付出的时候了
wasted, you can never down.
爱就在我身边 浪费了 你永远不能倒下
Why don't you take you mind?
你为什么不把你的心
Just me.
就我一个
Cnn oo.
CNN OO
So you, man,
所以你 伙计
la,
洛杉矶
I guess,
我猜
is a co d how are things in the world of sports?
体育世界里的事情怎么样
How would I know i'm the weatherman?
我怎么知道我是天气预报员
Why do I keep thinking you're a sportscaster?
为什么我一直以为你是体育节目主持人
Anyway, barry thinks you're doing a great job,though,
无论如何 巴里认为你做得很好
barry, our new station manager,
不过巴里 我们的新电台经理
the one we call mr.
我们叫他先生
Phelps,
费尔普斯
keep up the good work, gordie.
继续努力 戈迪
Our audience sure loves that great sports weather,
我们的观众肯定喜欢那种很棒的
stuff.
体育天气
Mary, what's that?
玛丽 那是什么
You have all over your dress?
你的衣服上到处都是
Yellow feathers.
黄色羽毛
That's what I thought.
我也是这么想的
Why do you have yellow feathers all over your dress?
为什么你的衣服上都是黄色的羽毛
Because I was trying to console big chicken.
因为我想安慰大鸡
I find it hard to sympathize with a grown man that puts on a chicken suit
我发现很难同情一个成年男子
every day and shows cartoons the 3 year old.
他每天穿着鸡服 给3岁的孩子看卡通片
Will murray you ought to try uncle potato got a higher rating
威尔·默里 你应该试试土豆叔叔得到了比大鸡更高的评价
than big chicken and mister phelps fired him?
而费尔普斯先生解雇了他
Gee, i'm sorry to hear that.
哎呀 听到这个消息我很难过
I he's really a nice guy.
他真的是个好人
Who are you sorry about him?
你为谁感到难过
Big chicken.
大鸡
Mr.
先生
Phelps just fired him.
费尔普斯刚刚解雇了他
Too bad.
太糟糕了
He was a great chicken.
他是一只很棒的鸡
Byebye.
拜拜
Ok.
好吧
No.
不
What is it?
那是什么
Ted?
泰德
Just my whole life, my whole career,my life.
我的一生 我的事业 我的生活
Can it wait?
能等吗
No,
不
they just fired big chicken since when have you ever been concerned
他们刚刚解雇了一只大鸡你什么时候开始关心另
about another human being?
一个人了
This time i'm concerned big chicken had a higher rating than I do.
这一次 我担心大鸡的评分比我高
We're wearing big chicken at a higher rating than all of us,
我们穿着比我们所有人都高的大鸡
but i'm not worried why should you.
但我并不担心你为什么要这样做
They always blame the star.
他们总是责怪明星
Besides,
另外
I don't think barry likes me.
我觉得巴里不喜欢我
Ted, he hasn't been here long enough,
泰德 他在这里的时间还不够长
not to like you.
不喜欢你
He's only been here a couple of weeks.
他才来了几个星期
It takes at least 3 weeks,
至少需要3个星期
not to like it.
不喜欢它
I know,
我知道
but he hasn't thanked me for my gift yet.
但是他还没有感谢我的礼物
You're still doing that,
你还在这样做
buying gifts for the new station managers.
给新的电台经理买礼物
I'll never forget what you got.
我永远不会忘记你所拥有的
The last one.
最后一个
$10.
He was a hard person to shop for.
他是个很难买东西的人
What did you get phelps that he didn't thank you for an autographed copy
你给费尔普斯买了什么
of winston churchill's memoirs.
他没有感谢你给他一本温斯顿·丘吉尔亲笔签名的回忆录
He was the prime minister of england.
他是英国的首相
Yeah, I heard a rumor.
是的 我听到了一个谣言
It's true.
这是真的
Where did you ever find a copy with churchill's autograph?
你在哪里找到过有丘吉尔亲笔签名的复制品
No, not churchill's mine that mary from ten
不 不是丘吉尔的我的 是十号的玛丽
should put my last name on it.
应该写上我的姓
Now he'll think it's ted martin of sales.
现在他会认为是销售部的泰德·马丁
What am I going to do?
我该怎么办
He's going to fire me.
他要解雇我
I just know he's going to fire me.
我只知道他会解雇我
I know it pen calm down.
我知道 但冷静点
Phelps doesn't own this station while jack monroe owns this station.
费尔普斯不拥有这个电台 而杰克·门罗拥有这个电台
I've seen a dozen phelps in that job since i've been here.
自从我到这里以来 我已经看到十几个费尔普斯在做那个工作
I feel like j edgar hoover watching presidents of the united states come
我觉得自己就像J·埃德加·胡佛（J Edgar Hoover）
and go.
看着美国总统来来去去
Now, if you're through,
现在 如果你通过了
i've got a tv show to put on.
我有一个电视节目要上演
Thanks.
谢谢
Nasa.
美国太空总署
Just a moment, please,
请稍等
ted telephone.
特德电话
We'll find out who it is.
我们会查出是谁的
It's mister phelps.
是费尔普斯先生
Hello, mr.
你好 先生
Phelps, sir.
费尔普斯先生
What now?
现在怎么办
No, i'm not busy.
不 我不忙
I'll be right there.
我马上到
I'll tell barry mr.
我会告诉巴里先生
Phelps wants to see us all immediately.
费尔普斯要马上见我们所有人
I'll get mister grant all except lou, let's go gang.
我去叫格兰特先生 除了卢 我们走吧
Where is everybody?
大家都去哪了
They went to the bank.
他们去了银行
Where are you going to the bank?
你要去哪里银行
Say hello to everybody for me.
代我向大家问好
Nano.
纳米
I'm sorry.
对不起
I haven't gotten to know everybody yet.
我还没有认识每一个人
I've only been on the job for 2 weeks, only a couple of weeks,
我只工作了两个星期
but you've done a heck of a job, right?
只有几个星期 但你做得很好 对吗
Then.
然后
I imagine you all know why we're here.
我想你们都知道我们为什么在这里
No, I don't.
不 我不知道
Our sales manager can sum it up for us if I can't sell the news if I
我们的销售经理可以为我们总结一下
can't sell the news,
如果我不能销售新闻
why not?
为什么不呢
Mary, why can't have sell the news?
玛丽 为什么不能把新闻卖掉
I don't know.
我不知道
Ev is one of the top men in his field.
伊夫是他所在领域的顶尖人物之一
That's why I listen hard when he says,
这就是为什么当他说“我不能卖新闻”时
I can't sell the news.
我会认真听
Barry,
巴里
i've been giving the problem serious thought and I can only say
我一直在认真考虑这个问题
that my fan mail is up 28%.
我只能说我的粉丝来信增加了28%
In other words,
换句话说
I feel the source of the situation may be behind the cameras.
我觉得这种情况的源头可能在摄像机后面
A gaudy, we haven't heard from you yet,
华而不实的是 我们还没有收到你的来信 顺便说一句
by the way, I must say you're doing crackerjack work,handling sports.
我必须说你在处理体育方面做得很出色
You're the weatherman,
玛丽
mary.
你是天气预报员
Someone is letting us down.
有人让我们失望了
Mister grant is very happy with the way everyone has been doing their job.
格兰特先生对每个人的工作方式都很满意
So if there's a problem,
所以如果有问题
shouldn't mister grant be?
格兰特先生不应该是吗
Here's precisely how would you judge lou grants work?
这正是你如何判断卢·格兰特的工作
I don't judge his work.
我不评价他的工作
He judges mine don't get upset, mary.
他判断我的别生气 玛丽
The matter has already been decided,
这件事已经决定了
decide.
决定
You can go agr
你可以走了
i'm sorry.
对不起
It took so long.
花了这么长时间
There was a long line at the bank.
银行里排着长队
Here it comes now.
现在它来了
More miserable lot.
更悲惨的一群人
I've never seen.
我从没见过
Hey, everybody,come on.
嘿 各位 来吧
Let's all have a meeting.
让我们都开个会吧
Now there's been lots of rumors going around about people being fired.
现在有很多关于人们被解雇的谣言
I just want to tell you all now that not one of you is going to be fired
我现在只想告诉你们 你们中没有一个人会被解雇
and that was a pep talk.
那是鼓舞士气的话
What's with you?
你怎么了
I have to go back to the bank.
我得回银行去
How do you like that?
你觉得怎么样
I give you a job security and right away you start taking advantage of me.
我给你工作保障 你马上就开始占我便宜
I was only kidding.
我只是在开玩笑
So
那么
be with us at 11:00 tonight when our whole wjm news team will be back.
今晚11点和我们在一起 那时我们整个WJM新闻团队都会回来
Gordie howard with the ladies and spore,
戈迪·霍华德与女士们和孢子
weather and yours,
天气和你的
truly ted baxter.
真正的泰德·巴克斯特
You then pretty good show tonight.
你今晚的表演很精彩
Good film, good pace.
好电影 好节奏
Only thing I didn't have was commercials.
我唯一没有的就是广告
Maybe that's why I had good pace.
也许这就是为什么我有很好的速度
Good show tonight, ted.
今晚的表演很精彩 泰德
Hey,
嘿
listen,
听着
i've got some ideas for some new features for the show to get a little possessed.
我有一些关于这个节目的新功能的想法 让你有点着魔
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
我们明天再谈
Say, if they're going to fire a guy,
比如说 如果他们要解雇一个人
why don't they just tell him instead of doing it like this?
为什么不直接告诉他而不是像这样做呢
I'll tell you one thing.
我要告诉你一件事
It's not going to be mr.
不会是先生
Phelps who tells him.
费尔普斯告诉他
You'd enjoy it too much.
你会很享受的
Good night.
晚安
Mary, I can't take it anymore.
玛丽 我再也受不了了
I know what you're thinking.
我知道你在想什么
And I can't take it.
我不能接受
I'm not thinking about you, ted,right?
我没在想你 泰德 对吧
I did blame lou for our low ratings.
我确实把我们的低收视率归咎于卢
Maybe I am the main reason he's being fired,
也许我是他被解雇的主要原因
but that doesn't mean I don't love him.
但这并不意味着我不爱他
Was either him or me.
不是他就是我
Can't you understand that?
你不明白吗
Put him down for a physical mister grant.
格兰特先生 把他的身体检查记录下来
I'd like to talk to you what's up.
我想和你谈谈怎么回事
A it's a little awkward,
A有点尴尬
but when I was at the bank today,
但我今天在银行的时候
I wasn't at the bank,
我当时
I was in mr.
不在银行
Phelps office.
费尔普斯办公室
Yeah, he sent for me.
是的 他派人来找我
You don't work for him.
你不为他工作
If he's dissatisfied with your work,
如果他对你的工作不满意
let him tell me about it.
让他告诉我
Mr.
先生
Grant.
格兰特
It's not my work that he's dissatisfied with.
他不满意的不是我的工作
That's what's been bugging you.
这就是一直困扰你的问题
Aren't you not by a long shot?
你是不是还差得远呢
I figured i'd get the axe.
我想我会得到斧头
You did?
是吗
I was worried for a while there that it wasn't gonna be me.
我担心过一段时间 那不会是我
It's probably the best thing that ever happened to me.
这可能是发生在我身上最好的事情
No, you're just saying that to make me feel better.
不 你这么说只是为了让我感觉好点
Now, look,
现在 听着
when you're in tv,
当你在电视台工作时
changing jobs is a way of life.
换工作是一种生活方式
10 years in one job is too long.
一份工作10年太长了
I've been turning down offer after offer for years,
多年来 我拒绝了一次又一次的邀请
just because I was too lazy to move.
只是因为我懒得搬家
All I have to do is just pick up the phone.
我要做的就是拿起电话
What can I get somebody for you?
有什么能帮你的吗
Would you mind waiting till they fire me?
你介意等他们解雇我吗
Please?
请
Would you get me?
你能帮我吗
Winnick, sid winnick?
温尼克 席德·温尼克
Yes, sir.
是的长官
Is mister winigan lou grants calling?
威尼根·卢·格兰特先生打电话来了吗
Thank you.
谢谢
Mr.
先生
Winning song, too.
获奖歌曲也是
Mr.
先生
Grant am say about that job,
格兰特：关于那份工作 我说
you've been pitching at me for 8.5 months.
你已经向我推销了8.5个月了
Is it now?
是现在吗
I'm suddenly available.
我突然有空了
I'm 45.
我45岁了
What's I got to do with anything?
这和我有什么关系
Youth movement.
青年运动
That's beautiful.
那很漂亮
You're 63 years old and you're having a youth movement.
你已经63岁了 你正在进行一场青年运动
I'm all in favor of your movement, sid.
席德 我完全赞成你的运动
Why don't you fire yourself?
你为什么不解雇你自己
If I had known, I was going to bomb,
如果我知道 我会爆炸
I would have shut the door.
我会把门关上
I'm sorry, a few months ago they had to have me.
对不起 几个月前他们不得不雇用我
But now that's just one.
但现在那只是一个
I you said you had lots of offers.
我你说你有很多工作机会
I did.
我做了
They were all from sid.
它们都来自席德
Mr.
先生
Phelps isn't the last word around here.
费尔普斯不是这里的最后一句话
It's wild jack monroe that owns this place.
这地方的主人是疯狂的杰克·门罗
What about him?
那他呢
I never should have left that old newspaper,
我本不该离开那份旧报纸
but it was those mergers that was driving me nuts.
但正是那些合并让我抓狂
I got tired of telling people I worked for the times globe herald journal chronicle.
我厌倦了告诉别人我为《泰晤士报》 《环球先驱报》和《纪事报》工作
I still should have stayed there.
我还是应该呆在那里
I got this job, I went into saloon,got drunk,
我得到了这份工作 我走进酒吧 喝醉了
fell down and met while jack monroe under a table.
摔倒了 然后在一张桌子下遇到了杰克·门罗
Where was that in hollywood?
那是在好莱坞什么地方
No, right here,never heard of a cowboy from minnesota.
不 就在这里 从没听说过明尼苏达州的牛仔
Guy made 300 grade b western zones,
盖伊在半个世界的西部地区创造了300个B级
half the world and lives on a ranch right outside minneapolis.
住在明尼阿波利斯郊外的一个牧场里
I think he raises snow.
我想他养了雪
Why don't you go see him?
你为什么不去看看他
Because i've got nothing to see him about.
因为我找他没什么事
That's why i'm not exactly.
这就是为什么我不完全是
I has been,
我一直在
hey, associate producer,
嘿 副制片人
what do you think you're doing?
你以为你在做什么
I thought you'd like to talk.
我以为你想谈谈
You are very nice.
你人很好
But what I really would like is to be alone.
但我真正想要的是独处
Okay.
好的
Nasa.
美国太空总署
Nasa,
美国国家航空航天局
45 years old.
45岁
If I was in politics,
如果我从政
they'd call me the kid.
他们会叫我小子
A
hi.
嗨
Did you get in touch with 40?
你和40联系上了吗
He's on his way.
他在路上了
Did you get?
你得到了吗
Ted?
泰德
I think so I called him 3 or 4 times.
我想是的 我给他打了三四次电话
And every time I mentioned that we were planning a strike, he hung up.
每次我提到我们计划罢工 他就挂断电话
The strike is out what my union won't.
罢工是我的工会不愿做的事
Let me, they'll only let me strike for what they want.
让我 他们只会让我为他们想要的东西而罢工
My union shop steward can't understand why I want to strike to save the job
我的工会商店管理员不能理解我为什么要罢工来保住管理
of someone in management.
人员的工作
What about a very strong protest?
非常强烈的抗议呢
That's one idea.
这是一个主意
We'll discuss it when the others get here.
等其他人来了我们再讨论
Would you like an order?
你要点菜吗
Mary, you weren't supposed to serve any?
玛丽 你不应该为任何人服务的
There wasn't any trouble.
没有任何麻烦
This is supposed to be a strike meeting.
这应该是一次罢工会议
I hate to tell you this, but when the teams does have a strike meeting,
我不想告诉你这个 但当球队举行罢工会议时
they only serve cold orders.
他们只提供冷冰冰的命令
Hi, 40.
嗨 40岁
Hi, mary.
嗨 玛丽
I think ted will be here in a minute.
我想泰德马上就到
What do you mean?
你什么意思
You think?
你觉得呢
When I was parking my car outside,
当我把车停在外面的时候
I saw him circling the block.
我看到他绕着街区转
He's probably afraid he's being followed.
他可能害怕被人跟踪
Yeah.
是啊
Ted doesn't exactly take it too lightly when he
当泰德认为有人会公开反对管理层时
thinks someone's gonna speak out against management.
他不会太掉以轻心
Okay?
好的
By the way, I can't strike what?
顺便问一下 我不能打什么
Your union to my wife.
你和我妻子的结合
She just told me we're gonna have another baby.
她刚告诉我我们又要有孩子了
40.
Congratulations.
祝贺
That's marvelous.
那太棒了
What are you hoping for a boy or a girl?
你想要什么 男孩还是女孩
We got a girl, so I hope it's a boy or girls babies.
我们得到了一个女孩 所以我希望它是一个男孩或女孩的婴儿
This isn't a protest meeting.
这不是抗议集会
It's a party.
这是一个聚会
Frank evans, I thought we were having a protest meeting.
弗兰克·埃文斯 我以为我们在举行抗议集会
Look who dropped in.
看看谁来了
What'd you do get tired of driving around the block?
你为什么会厌倦开车绕着街区转
You saw me coming.
你看到我来了
I wonder if anyone else did.
我想知道是否还有其他人
Ted, I someone from the other side,your other side,not mine.
泰德 我是来自另一个世界的人 你的另一个世界 不是我的
I'm not taking part in this.
我不会参与这件事
Ted.
泰德
Will you please come in and relax?
请你进来放松一下好吗
No one saw you come in here,
没人看到你进来
but we need you.
但我们需要你
I never thought i'd say this,
我从没想过我会这么说
but you're the strongest weapon.
但你是最强大的武器
We've got.
我们有
We just lost.
我们刚刚输了
I know,
我知道
you think i'm afraid to join in with you.
你认为我害怕加入你的行列
Don't you bet i'm here?
你不打赌我在这里吗
Aren't I I made a decision to come here and listen to your arguments.
不是吗 我决定来这里听你们的辩论
And if they're strong enough,
如果他们足够强大
i'll stand with you 100%.
我会100%支持你
Okay, all right.
好的 好的
Lou grant is the best news director our station has ever had,
卢·格兰特是我们电视台有史以来最好的新闻总监
and he is about to be fired by a man who knows absolutely nothing about news.
而他即将被一个对新闻一窍不通的人解雇
He is right.
他是对的
Plus the fact that every one of us in this room owes him so much,
再加上我们在座的每一个人都欠他太多
we couldn't ever repay him, add to that.
我们永远无法报答他 再加上这一点
The fact that when some of us thought that our jobs were in jeopardy,
事实上 当我们中的一些人认为我们的工作处于危险之中时
it was lou grant who was the first to put his job on the line for us.
是卢·格兰特第一个把他的工作置于危险之中
That's right.
对的
I'm afraid you're gonna have to do better than that.
恐怕你得做得更好
My god.
我的天哪
The only way we're gonna get them on our side is to convince them
唯一能让他们站在我们这边的方法就是让他们相信这
there's more money in this.
里面有更多的钱
I just don't like this strike business.
我只是不喜欢这种罢工
We aren't gonna strike ted.
我们不会攻击泰德的
No, we're just thinking about presenting phelps with some kind of petition.
不 我们只是在考虑给费尔普斯一些请愿书
What good is a petition with three names on it?
有三个名字的请愿书有什么用
But we're four.
但我们是四个人
No, you're three.
不 你三岁了
I vote.
我投票
We throw them out now.
我们现在就把他们扔出去
Wait a minute, marie.
等一下 玛丽
Maybe ted has some ideas on this.
也许泰德对此有一些想法
Ted, if you were about to lose your job,no,
泰德 如果你要失业了 不
i'm not about to lose my job.
我不会失业的
I I I know.
我我我知道
But if you were,
但如果你是
What would you do?
你会怎么做
You mean if Phelps were about to fire me?
你是说如果费尔普斯要解雇我
I'd see the man who owns the station while Jack Monroe,
我要去见电视台的老板 而杰克·门罗
that's not a bad idea.
这主意不错
Maybe lu should go see him.
也许卢应该去看看他
No, mister grant would never beg when you see,no,
不 格兰特先生永远不会乞求 当你看到
that's exactly what I mean.
不 这正是我的意思
How can you help a man who refuses to beg?
你怎么能帮助一个拒绝乞讨的人呢
What if all of us went to see him?
如果我们所有人都去看他呢
Are you kidding with a name like that?
你用这样的名字开玩笑吗
He must really be a weirdo?
他一定是个怪人
Murray.
默里
All cowboys have names like that.
所有牛仔都有这样的名字
He was just Jack Monroe in the movies.
他只是电影里的杰克·门罗
He got the wild just for being himself.
他只是因为做自己而得到了野性
Look, Mary,I think a girl should go see him.
听着 玛丽 我觉得一个女孩应该去看看他
Why?
为什么
Because the guys don't want it.
因为那些家伙不想要它
All right.
好吧
I will go see you while Jack Monroe gaudy.
我会去看你 而杰克·门罗
How weird is he?
他有多奇怪
He is weird.
他很奇怪
Listen, I came to see you about Lou grant.
听着 我来找你是为了卢·格兰特的事
Lou grant,
卢·格兰特
he said that you personally hired him to be the news director
他说你亲自聘请他担任wjm电视台的
at wjm my station here in town.
新闻总监我在城里的电视台
Mister Phelps is gonna fire him.
费尔普斯先生要解雇他
Slim Phelps, my new station manager.
斯利姆·费尔普斯我的新电台经理
He's going to fire him,
他要解雇他 先生
sir, what's the matter?
怎么了
Is he one of them?
他是其中之一吗
Radicals?
激进分子
Mister grant?
格兰特先生
No.
不
I'm always kidding him about being too conservative.
我总是跟他开玩笑说他太保守了
Young lady.
年轻的女士
There ain't no such a thing as being too conservative.
没有太保守这回事
I I said I was kidding.
我我说我是开玩笑的
That's one thing.
那是一回事
You can't be too careful these days.
这些天你再小心也不为过
What with them?
他们怎么了
Long haired hippies are running around with them,
长发嬉皮士和他们一起跑来跑去
wild clothes on while I can.
在我可以的时候穿着狂野的衣服
Okay, I'm a cowboy.
好吧 我是个牛仔
I think I need a shot who gets on.
我想我需要拍一张谁上车
They are fired me better.
他们解雇了我更好
How old is this?
这是多少年前的
Your grant?
你的助学金
Bella?
贝拉
He's 45,
他45岁了
amazing.
太棒了
45.
It's on my 45th birthday at the studio called me in and told me I was through.
在我45岁生日的时候 工作室打电话给我 告诉我我已经结束了
That's when I found out that building that they fired me in.
就在那时我发现了他们解雇我的那栋楼
I owned it.
我拥有它
You didn't know that.
你不知道
You see, I had this here at Campbell,
你看 我在坎贝尔有这个 但没有一个是属于我的
and none belongs to me why he'd been investing my money for me.
为什么他一直在为我投资
You name it?
你说吧
I owned it, lock stock and barrel,
我拥有它 全部的股票和木桶
thanks to good old slim shorts.
感谢好旧的苗条短裤
That would be your accountant.
那是你的会计
And I thought I was worse stuff and you weren't.
我以为我是更坏的东西 而你不是
And neither is Lou grant.
卢·格兰特也不是
That's why I came to see you.
这就是我来找你的原因
I make it a point not to butt into the way my business is handled,
我不会干涉我的业务处理方式
but let me just kind of twist it around in my mind a while.
但让我在脑海中扭转一下
I'll be getting back to your mister Richards.
我会回到你的理查兹先生那里
I'll be a senior slim, okay?
我会成为一名资深的斯利姆 好吗
Iiisa.
三世
Nana,
娜娜
miss MR.
先生小姐
Grant finally got it.
格兰特终于拿到了
You want to know something those pink slips you get.
你想知道你收到的那些解雇通知书吗
They really are pink, red.
它们真的是粉红色 红色的
That's what pink slips should be or black.
这就是解雇通知书应该是黑色的
You fire a ballerina with a pink slip,
你用解雇通知书解雇了一个芭蕾舞演员
not a newsman.
而不是一个新闻记者
But MR.
但是先生
Quinn don't talk.
奎恩 别说话
You start talking pretty soon.
你很快就开始说话了
You'll be trying to organize a farewell party with punch and cupcakes.
你要组织一场有潘趣酒和纸杯蛋糕的告别派对
Everybody will chip in and buy me a shaving kit for a going away present.
每个人都会凑钱给我买一套剃须用具作为临别礼物
There'll be a secretary,
会有一个秘书
they'll come over to me and she'll do this.
他们会来找我 她会做这件事
Not, for me,
不 对我来说
mister grant look at what I'm trying to tell you is you might not have to leave.
格兰特先生看 我想告诉你的是 你可能不需要离开
I went to see Weil, Jack Monroe.
我去见了韦尔 杰克·门罗
I do not remember asking you for any help.
我不记得向你寻求过任何帮助
Here's the last order.
这是最后一道菜
I can give you Mary lay off.
我可以让你和玛丽分手
I don't lay off.
我不会放弃
Lou.
娄
I just wanted to give you this little token of mine.
我只是想给你我的这个小礼物
It's a shaving kit.
这是一套剃须用具
Thanks.
谢谢
I'm getting out of here.
我要离开这里
Which one is Lou grant?
哪个是卢·格兰特
Nasa.
美国太空总署
I'm Lou grant.
我是卢·格兰特
What about it?
那又怎么样
I want to talk to you in private.
我想和你私下谈谈
Let's go on my office now.
我们现在去我的办公室吧
While Jack Monroe talks private,
当杰克·门罗私下谈话时
he don't go Lego.
他不会去乐高
Hey, you swim,
嘿 你游泳
you're doing a great job with that sports news.
你在体育新闻方面做得很好
Keep it up.
跟进
I said, keep it up.
我说 继续努力
Don't worry.
别担心
We'll get 100 Indians and come back.
我们会带100个印第安人回来
I'm not you, little lady.
我不是你 小姑娘
Hi, ya.
嗨 雅
Didn't you and me have a hoop to do one time or other?
你和我不是总有一次要练篮球吗
You could call it that I lost four teeth myself.
你可以说我自己掉了四颗牙
Day that is the best day fight I ever had.
那天是我经历过的最好的一天
The little lady tells me you're getting fired.
这位女士告诉我你要被解雇了
Little lady's got a big mouth.
小女人有个大嘴巴
I'll watch that boy, that's a woman,
我会看着那个男孩 那是个女人
but it's a woman with a big mouth.
但那是个大嘴巴的女人
See what mister grant means is that I I do not need an interpreter.
格兰特先生的意思是我不需要翻译
I don't need any favors from you.
我不需要你的任何帮助
I don't want this job.
我不想要这份工作
I work someplace else.
我在别的地方工作
I got ATV station in Boise, Idaho.
我在爱达荷州的博伊西有一家ATV电视台
Keep talking.
继续说
You got the job.
你得到工作了
Hey, what?
嘿 怎么了
I got a shaving kit and a job in Boise, Idaho.
我在爱达荷州的博伊西找到一套剃须工具和一份工作
Boxed you that time I already got me ATV news director in Boise, Idaho.
那次我已经在爱达荷州的博伊西找到了我的亚视新闻总监
I'll have to transfer you to in there.
我得把你转到里面去
Come on out to the range house.
到牧场来吧
Sometime.
有时
We'll open up a cake of nails.
我们要打开一块钉子蛋糕
Welcome back.
欢迎回来
I suppose you feel like Mary Poppins or something.
我猜你觉得自己像玛丽·波平斯什么的
No, actually,I'm a little disappointed.
不 实际上 我有点失望
I thought I was next in line for your job.
我以为我是你的下一个工作人选
Nasa.
美国太空总署
What kind of a going away card?
什么样的告别卡
Is this to Lou from Ted?
这是泰德给卢的吗
Forgive me, but I'm weak.
原谅我 但我很虚弱
That could mean 1 million things.
这可能意味着一百万件事
Could mean he's weak.
可能意味着他很虚弱
How do you go about giving back a shaving kit?
你是怎么把剃须刀还回去的
I don't know, i've never had one as a gift.
我不知道 我从来没有收到过礼物
I never have either.
我也从来没有
I think i'll keep this one.
我想我会留着这个
Sometimes I don't know whether I'm working or hallucinate ing.
有时我不知道自己是在工作还是在幻觉
Big chicken's back turns out the big chicken is wild Jack Monroe favorite show.
大鸡回来了原来大鸡是野生杰克·门罗最喜欢的节目
Nasa.
美国太空总署
Byebye.
拜拜
Nasa.
美国太空总署